The Peoples of the Pirá-Paraná Collection of Stephen Hugh-Jones and Christine Hugh-Jones
Nettie Lee Benson Latin American Collection,
- Open Reel Audiotapes
  - Myth
    - [>2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Woman who made cassav bread at night story, undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] ~Dikorete, ~Bosiro keti (Nikorete toad and Cricket story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_02_ac.mp3] Buo keti (Agouti Woman in the underworld story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_02_ac.mp3] ~Waribi keti (Warimi story), undated (Box 7, Item 81)
  - Description
    Boxes 4 and 5 housed in LSF container B, Boxes 6 and 7 housed in LSF container C
    - [2019_0251_0002_01_ac.mp3] Information on Kawayaria and other Wai ~Basa (Fish People) groups, 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] ~Guta yaiya (Stone jaguars - about fossils, 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Yoke~ra ~basa; Eri Bühühogo keti (on spooky people; Bushmaster and Owl story), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] On wekü ~budi (tapir-bone coca scoop) and other ritual gear, 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] Clarification of Arrival of Barasana sibs, ~Robi ~Kubu and Hee ~Basa, 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_01_ac.mp3] More clarification of Arrival of Barasana sibs, ~Robi ~Kubu and Hee ~Basa, 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] About illegitimate Hee, bees, beeswax, death, life-cycle, stars, etc, 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0004_02_ac.mp3] On Hee instruments ('Yuruparí'), undated (Box 4, Item 64)
    - [2019_0251_0007_02_ac.mp3] Childbirth rites, undated (Box 4, Item 67)
    - [2019_0251_0007_02_ac.mp3] Magic bird feather for getting women, undated (Box 4, Item 67)
    - [2019_0251_0007_02_ac.mp3] Sib order, housing, feuds in past, undated (Box 4, Item 67)
    - [2019_0251_0007_02_ac.mp3] Use of masked dances (yago sudia, bohori ~watia) in pasttime mourning rituals, undated (Box 4, Item 67)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Ceremonial partners at initiation rites (~Heyeri/~Heyerio relation), undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0012_01_ac.mp3] About chagras, undated (Box 5, Item 72)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] Describes Villavicencio in Bará (his own language), undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] On groups, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] Post-initiation restrictions, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0015_01_ac.mp3] Account of Pacho Tukano on seasons, undated (Box 6, Item 75)
    - [2019_0251_0016_01_ac.mp3] Animal names (in Makuna language), undated (Box 6, Item 76)
    - [2019_0251_0016_01_ac.mp3] Animals names and language (in Makuna), undated (Box 6, Item 76)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] Ceremonial partners at initiation rites (~Heyeri/~Heyerio relation), undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] On marriage morals, undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0018_01_ac.mp3] Results of breaking food restrictions, undated (Box 6, Item 78)
    - [2019_0251_0018_01_ac.mp3] Macaws, undated (Box 6, Item 78)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] On womens' work at dances, undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] About CHJ going alone to Bogotá, undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] About Yuruparí and CHJ going to Bogotá, undated (Box 6, Item 79)
  - Conversation
    - [2019_0251_0002_02_ac.mp3] Talk about ~watia (spirits), 1970 (Box 4, Item 62)
    - [2019_0251_0003_02_ac.mp3] On snakes and chagras, 1970 (Box 4, Item 63)
    - [2019_0251_0012_01_ac.mp3] Dialogue related to offering coca, undated (Box 5, Item 72)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] On marriage morals, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] On marriage morals, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] Conversation, undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] untitled, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
  - Music
    - [2019_0251_0005_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, Yapurutú, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 4, Item 65)
    - [2019_0251_0007_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, Tortoise w. panpipe, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 4, Item 67)
    - [2019_0251_0008_01_ac.mp3] Silly songs, undated (Box 4, Item 68)
    - [2019_0251_0008_01_ac.mp3] Whistle; playing around; Kawiyerí language, account of Pasico's return fr. Komenya (contd. T8R), undated (Box 4, Item 68)
    - [2019_0251_0008_02_ac.mp3] Contd. Fr T8G, undated (Box 4, Item 68)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Tortoise shell w. solo panpipe, undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0010_01_ac.mp3] ~Rabe basa (Rame's song), undated (Box 5, Item 70)
    - [2019_0251_0016_01_ac.mp3] Dance song, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 6, Item 76)
    - [2019_0251_0017_01_ac.mp3] Sings dance songs, undated (Box 6, Item 77)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Singing, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Dance music, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Singing/talking in Tukano, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Singing, playing, whistle, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes; dance song, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_02_ac.mp3] Hee (Yuruparí), undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Song, undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Dance song, undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_01_ac.mp3] Chonta dances fr Komenya, undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0021_02_ac.mp3] Chonta dances fr Komenya contd, undated (Box 7, Item 81)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3]Various dance sounds, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Besuwü Yukü (Rattle kance), undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] ~Yaba Rihoa (Deer Skul Ocarina), undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Coca pounding at night - rec. fr outside house, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Mission sounds, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0023_01_ac.mp3] Hee ("yuruparí") flutes over men's chatter at ritual, undated (Box 7, Item 126)
    - [2019_0251_0023_02_ac.mp3] Hee, dancing, panpipes, chatter at ritual, undated (Box 7, Item 126)
    - [2019_0251_0024_01_ac.mp3] (War of the Gods recordings), undated (Box 7, Item 127)
    - [2019_0251_0025_01_ac.mp3] (War of the Gods recordings), undated (Box 7, Item 128)
    - [2019_0251_0026_01_ac.mp3] (War of the Gods recordings), undated (Box 7, Item 129)
    - [2019_0251_0027_01_ac.mp3] (War of the Gods recordings), undated (Box 7, Item 130)
  - Ritual
    - [2019_0251_0005_01_ac.mp3] Sounds of dancing and chanting, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 4, Item 65)
    - [2019_0251_0006_01_ac.mp3] Panpipes, dancing, chanting, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 4, Item 66)
    - [2019_0251_0009_02_ac.mp3] Dancing and chanting, undated (Box 5, Item 69)
    - [2019_0251_0016_02_ac.mp3] Dancing and singing, 1968 October-1968 November (Box 6, Item 76)
    - [2019_0251_0019_01_ac.mp3] Dance, chant, panpipe dances, undated (Box 6, Item 79)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Hia Basa (Side Dance) and converation, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
    - [2019_0251_0022_01_ac.mp3] Dance sounds and conversation, undated (Box 7, Item 82)
  - Commentary
    Box 5 housed in LSF container B, Boxes 6 and 7 housed in LSF container C
    - [2019_0251_0013_02_ac.mp3] Of no value, undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] Explanation of characters in mythology; of coca ritual, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0014_01_ac.mp3] On shamanism, group origins, eclipses etc, undated (Box 5, Item 74)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] untitled play, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_01_ac.mp3] Whistle and play, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
    - [2019_0251_0020_02_ac.mp3] Playing and singing, undated (Box 6, Item 80)
  - Chant
    Box 4 housed in LSF container B, Box 7 housed in LSF container C
    - [2019_0251_0008_02_ac.mp3] Solo chanting in non-ritual context, undated (Box 4, Item 68)
    - [2019_0251_0023_01_ac.mp3] In ritual context; preceeded by ceremonial greeting and coca exchange, undated (Box 7, Item 126)
    - [2019_0251_0023_01_ac.mp3] untitled chant, undated (Box 7, Item 126)
    - [2019_0251_0023_02_ac.mp3] untitled chant, undated (Box 7, Item 126)
  - Miscellaneous
    Box 5 housed in LSF container B, Box 6 housed in LSF container C
    - [2019_0251_0013_01_ac.mp3] Blank, undated (Box 5, Item 73)
    - [2019_0251_0020_02_ac.mp3] untitled, undated (Box 6, Item 80)